Guide to the UTU Records
UTU Records
- Portland Terminal Railroad (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Quantity Tables (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Rail Labor Statistics- U. Illinois (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Reimbursed Expenses (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Report of General Secretary/Treasurer (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Reports, Minutes, Speeches, Presentations, Charts (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Sec. 6 Minutes (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Southern Pacific (P) GS-892 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Sou. Pac. -Local 158- GS 893 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Sou. Pac.- Local 164 - GS-894 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Southern Pacific (A) GS-895 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Springfield Terminal (Box 10, Folder 21)
- St. Louis Gateway (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Texas A&M University (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Thesis on Transportation Planning and History (Box 10, Folder 24)
  Unnamed and undated thesis paper, most likely a Master's, but not ruling out an undergraduate thesis.
- Transportation- Logistics (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Transportation Research (Box 10, Folder 26)
- UTU Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 27)
- UTU Records Division 15 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- UTU Young Leaders Conference (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Wage Rules- 1981 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Wage Rules- Dispute (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Western Pacific (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Workshop (RLEA) (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Arbitrations: Findings and Awards I (Box 10.1, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations: Findings and Awards II (Box 10.1, Folder 2)
- Arbitrations: Awards, Dissent, Implementation (Box 10.1, Folder 3)
- Arbitrations: New York Dock Conditions (Box 10.1, Folder 4)
- Brief (Box 10.1, Folder 5)
- Civil Action #82 (Box 10.1, Folder 6)
- Complaint (Box 10.1, Folder 7)
- Congressional/Federal Regulations (Box 10.1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence (Box 10.1, Folder 9)
- Court of Appeals (Box 10.1, Folder 10)
- District Court (Box 10.1, Folder 11)
- Special Court (Box 10.1, Folder 12)
- Supreme Court Cases (Box 10.1, Folder 13)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 1: Statement of Charles I. Hopkins, Jr. (Box 10.1, Folder 14)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 3: Intermodal Competition (Box 10.1, Folder 15)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 4: The Pay Rules Issue (BLE) (Box 10.1, Folder 16)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 5: The Pay Rules Issue (UTU) (Box 10.1, Folder 17)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 6: Arbitraries as Percent of Annual Earnings (Box 10.1, Folder 18)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 7: Earnings Study (Box 10.1, Folder 19)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 8: Arbitraries and/or Special Allowances on Selected Railroads (Box 10.1, Folder 20)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 9: The Holddown Issue and the Caboose Issue, AT & SF Railway (Box 10.1, Folder 21)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 10: The Holddown Issue: N&W Railway (Box 10.1, Folder 22)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 11: The Caboose Issue (Box 10.1, Folder 23)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 12: Meal Allowance Issue (Box 10.1, Folder 24)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 13: Joint Labor/Mgmt. Commission and General Provisions (Box 10.1, Folder 25)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 20: The UTU Case (Box 10.1, Folder 26)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195- Carrier's Exhibit No. 21: Subject Matter Compilation of Transcripts & Exhibits Governing Direct Presentations (Box 10.1, Folder 27)
- Emergency Board No. 195: Index of UTU Exhibits (Box 10.1, Folder 28)
- Emergency Board No. 195- Exhibit 14: Part 1, Folder 1 (Box 10.1, Folder 29)
- Emergency Board No. 195- Exhibit 14: Part 1, Folder 2 (Box 10.2, Folder 1)
- Emergency Board No. 195- Exhibit 14: Part 2, Folder 1 (Box 10.2, Folder 2)
- Emergency Board No. 195- Exhibit 14: Part 2, Folder 2 (Box 10.2, Folder 3)
- Emergency Board No. 195- Exhibit 14: Part 3, Folder 1 (Box 10.2, Folder 4)
- Emergency Board No. 195- Exhibit 14: Part 3, Folder 2 (Box 10.2, Folder 5)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195: Transcript 1 of 3 (Box 10.2, Folder 6)
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195: Transcript 2 of 3 (Box 10.2, Folder 7)
  Part 2 of 3
- Emergency Board No. 194 and 195: Transcript 3 of 3 (Box 10.2, Folder 8)
  Part 3 of 3
- Emergency Board No. 195: Transcript (Box 10.2, Folder 9)
- Implementation and Notifications (Box 10.2, Folder 10)
- Index Digests (Box 10.2, Folder 11)
- Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC) Docket (Box 10.2, Folder 12)
- National Mediation Board (Box 10.2, Folder 13)
- President's Report (Box 10.2, Folder 14)
- Public Law Board I (Box 10.2, Folder 15)
- Public Law Board II (Box 10.2, Folder 16)
- Special Board of Adjustment (Box 10.2, Folder 17)
- State Legislative Board Documents (Box 10.2, Folder 18)
- Statements and Transcripts (Box 10.2, Folder 19)
- Statements: Fred Hardin (Box 10.2, Folder 20)
- Alcoholism/Drug Abuse (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Alcoholism/Drug Abuse: DOT/FRA (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Documents pertaining to the Department of Transportation and the Federal Railroad Administration
- Arbitration Reports (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Award Circulars, Pt. 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Award Circulars, Pt. 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Award Circulars, Pt. 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- BLE/UTU (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Crew Consist (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Directory/Telephone Numbers (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Election to General Committee of Adjustment (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Elections, Votes (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Gen. Committee Of Adjustment (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Gen. Committee Of Adjustment Assessments: July '75 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Gen. Committee Of Adjustment Assessments: Sept. '80 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Gen. Committee Of Adjustment Assessments: Sept. '81 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment Assessments: June '82 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment Assessments: Aug. '83 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment Assessments: April '84 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment: Local Chairmen (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment (E): 1969 Agreement, Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment (E): 1969 Agreement, Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Gen. Committee of Adjustment: Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Letters: H&W (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Letters: M/T (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Letters: WR's (Box 11.1, Folder 1)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1970-75 (Box 11.1, Folder 2)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1981, Pt. 1 (Box 11.1, Folder 3)
- Letters-- SSRs: 1981, Pt. 2 (Box 11.1, Folder 4)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1981, Pt. 3 (Box 11.1, Folder 5)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1981, Pt. 4 (Box 11.1, Folder 6)
- Letters-- SSR's:1981, Pt. 5 (Box 11.1, Folder 7)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1981, Pt. 6 (Box 11.1, Folder 8)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1983, Pt. 1 (Box 11.1, Folder 9)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1983, Pt. 2 (Box 11.1, Folder 10)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1983, Pt. 3 (Box 11.1, Folder 11)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1983, Pt. 4 (Box 11.1, Folder 12)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1983, Pt. 5 (Box 11.1, Folder 13)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1983, Pt. 6 (Box 11.1, Folder 14)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1986, Pt. 1 (Box 11.1, Folder 15)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1986, Pt. 2 (Box 11.2, Folder 1)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1987, Pt. 1 (Box 11.2, Folder 2)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1987, Pt. 2 (Box 11.2, Folder 3)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1987, Pt. 3 (Box 11.2, Folder 4)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1987, Pt. 4 (Box 11.2, Folder 5)
- Letters-- SSR's: 1987, Pt. 5 (Box 11.3, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11.3, Folder 2)
- National Mediation Board (Box 11.3, Folder 3)
- Newsletters (Box 11.3, Folder 4)
- Procedure for Filing Protests to Alleged Violations (Box 11.3, Folder 5)
- Public Law Board (Box 11.3, Folder 6)
- Quarterly Reports (Box 11.3, Folder 7)
- Salaries & Expenses of the General Adjustment Committee (Box 11.3, Folder 8)
- Semi-Annual Reports (Box 11.3, Folder 9)
- Special Board of Adjustment (Box 11.3, Folder 10)
- TWU/UTU (Box 11.3, Folder 11)
- UTU Organizer's Handbook (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Organizing Organizing Materials Misc. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Organizing Requests (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Organizing Materials Misc. (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Rock Island and Milwaukee Bankruptcy 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Milw.- Workshop Evaluation 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Interim Report of the Task Force on Rail Transportation of Hazardous Materials (Box 13.1, Folder 1)
- Buffalo Terminal Improvement Project (Box 13.1, Folder 2)
- Buffalo (Depew) Task Force (Box 13.1, Folder 3)
- Chicago Terminal (Box 13.1, Folder 4)
- Grand Trunk, 1974 (Box 13.2, Folder 1)
- St. Louis- 1981 (Box 13.2, Folder 2)
- St. Louis- Expansion (Box 13.2, Folder 3)
- Misc. Task Force (Box 13.2, Folder 4)
- Chicago Task Force (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Cleveland Task Force (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Houston Task Force (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Terminal Project (Box 14.1, Folder 1)
- Portland Terminal Project (Box 14.1, Folder 2)
- St. Louis Terminal Project (Box 14.1, Folder 3)
- Final Report of St. Louis Terminal Project (Box 14.1, Folder 4)
- Experiments- Taskforce (Box 15, Folder 1)
- St. Louis Task Force (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Task Force Budget- '75, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- '76 Budget, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Progress Reports to AAR. (Box 15.1, Folder 1)
- E-W Gateway St. Louis (Box 15.1, Folder 2)
- Mo Pac- St. Louis (Box 15.1, Folder 3)
- St. Louis Terminal Operations (Box 15.1, Folder 4)
- Task Force- Department of Transportation (Box 15.1, Folder 5)
- 1975 Progress Report (Box 15.1, Folder 6)
- Labor and Management Committee: St. Louis Pilot Project Proposal (Box 15.1, Folder 7)
- Labor Management Cooperation in Multicarrier Rail Terminals (Box 15.2, Folder 1)
- A Program of Experiments: 1974 Progress Report (Box 15.2, Folder 2)
- A Program of Operations Involving Changes in Terminal Operations: 1974 Progress Report (Box 15.2, Folder 3)
- The Task Force on Terminals:1974 Progress Report (Box 15.2, Folder 4)
- Task Force on Terminals Progress Report for Year 1974 (Box 15.2, Folder 5)
- Task Force 1977 (Box 15.2, Folder 6)
- LM Task Force- Bus (Box 15.3, Folder 1)
- Gov't Task Force (General) (Box 15.3, Folder 2)
- Vancouver Rail Task Force (Box 15.3, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Task Force (Box 15.4, Folder 1)
- New England Task Force (Box 15.4, Folder 2)
- Erie Group/ Southern Tier- NY C.R. (Box 15.4, Folder 3)
- ThI Meeting (Box 15.4, Folder 4)
- Task Force Correspondence (Box 15.4, Folder 5)
- Short Crew Agreements (Box 15.4, Folder 6)
- Task Force- Other (Buffalo, Ohio) (Box 15.4, Folder 7)
- Task Force Meeting August 12, 1975 St. Louis, Missouri (Box 15.4, Folder 8)
- A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 15.4, Folder 9)
- Operation CO-OP Committee on Operation Planning (Box 15.4, Folder 10)
- Board of Appeals (Other) (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Board of Appeals- "S" (Box 16, Folder 2)
- (Box 16, Folder 3)
- 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Appeals- 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Jan. 27, 1982 Agreement (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Board No. 387 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Board No. 419 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- 1970 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 5)
- 1970 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 6)
- 1980 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 7)
- 1971 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 8)
- 1972 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 9)
- 1974 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 10)
- 1969 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 1969 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 18, Folder 12)
- 1979 Board of Appeals Report (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Board of Appeals Cases- 7/15-8/27/80, 1980 (Box 18.1, Folder 1)
- Bd. Of Appeals- Jan. '81, 1981 (Box 18.1, Folder 2)
- Bd. of Appeals- Mar. '83, 1983 (Box 18.1, Folder 3)
- Bd. of Appeals- 10/85, 1985 (Box 18.1, Folder 4)
- Bd. Of Appeals- 8/85, 1985 (Box 18.1, Folder 5)
- March- April of '86, appeals, cases, etc., 1986 (Box 18.1, Folder 6)
- UTU Appeal Cases 11-14, 203-214, 217, 324-326, 328 (Box 18.1, Folder 7)
- Bd. Of Appeals- March 1982 (Box 18.2, Folder 1)
- Bd. of Appeals 10/83, 1983 (Box 18.2, Folder 2)
- Bd. of Appeals- 2/84, 1984 (Box 18.2, Folder 3)
- Bd. of Appeals- 3/85, 1985 (Box 18.2, Folder 4)
- Case Files (Box 18.2, Folder 5)
- "Washington Report" (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Misc. (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Empire State Views (Box 20, Folder 1)
- News- Grams (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Quarterly Reports (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Statements Made Before the Traffic Executive Asso.- E.RR's Public Hearing No. 194, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- By-Laws of the NY State Legislative Board (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Calif. (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Colorado (Box 21, Folder 2)
- General- (state legislative boards) (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Indiana (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Iowa (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Ill. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Maine (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Missouri (Box 21, Folder 8)
- New England (Box 21, Folder 9)
- North Dakota (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Ohio (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Penn. (Box 21, Folder 12)
- (Box 21, Folder 13)
- "Economic Impact Analysis: Proposed Abandonment of the Pierre to Rapid City Rail Line" (Box 21.1, Folder 1)
- "Let's Make a Deal" (Box 21.1, Folder 2)
- State Director's Report to the South Dakota Legislative Board.. No. 11-83 (Box 21.1, Folder 3)
- Railplan South Dakota- 1983 (Box 21.1, Folder 4)
- Addendum to Railplan South Dakota- 1983 (Box 21.1, Folder 5)
- Executive Summary: Railplan South Dakota- 1980 (Box 21.1, Folder 6)
- Affidavit of S.F.A. McGregor, 1985 (Box 21.1, Folder 7)
- So. Dakota (Box 21.1, Folder 8)
- So. Dakota (Box 21.1, Folder 9)
- Tennessee (Box 21.1, Folder 10)
- Texas (Box 21.1, Folder 11)
- Utah (Box 21.1, Folder 12)
- Wash. State (Box 21.1, Folder 13)
- West Virginia (Box 21.1, Folder 14)
- (Box 21.1, Folder 15)
- SSR Letters: (1-69)-(12-69) (Box 22, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (13-69)-(25-69) (Box 22, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (26-69)-(35-69) (Box 22, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (36-69)-(40-69) (Box 22, Folder 4)
- UTU General Committees of Adjustment in the United States: Report to the President, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Awards- Misc. (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Awards- Discipline- Accident Responsibility, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Awards- Misc., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Awards- Procedural Awards, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Awards- Meal Period, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- SSR Letters: (1-70)-(20-70) missing (6-70) (Box 23, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (21-70)-(29-70) (Box 23, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (35-70)-(45-70) (Box 23, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (46-70)-(53-70) (Box 23, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (1-71)-(12-71) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (13-71)-(19-71) (Box 24, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (21-71)-(32-71) (Box 24, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (1-72)-(15-72) (Box 25, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: 917-720-(26-72) missing (22-72) (Box 25, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (1-73)-(15-73) missing (9-73) (Box 25, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (17-73)-(24-73) (Box 25, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (4-74) and (6-74) (Box 25, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (52-78)-(57-78) (Box 25, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (39-79), (61-79)-(71-79) (Box 26, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (73-79)-(85-79) (Box 26, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters:(86-79)- (95-79) (Box 26, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (96-79)- (101-79) (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Misc. Awards, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (75-80)-(90-80) (Box 27, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (91-80)-(105-80) (Box 27, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (106-80)-(120-80) (Box 27, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (121-80)-(125-80) (Box 27, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (11-86)- (16-86) (Box 27, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (6-86)-(10-86) (Box 27, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (17-86)-(30-86) (Box 27, Folder 7)
- SSR Letters: (36-86)-(45-86) and (50-86) (Box 28, Folder 1)
- SSR Letter: (91-85) (Box 28, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (1-80)-(20-80) (Box 28, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (23-80)-(40-80) (Box 28, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (41-80)-(55-80) (Box 28, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (56-80)-(70-80) (Box 28, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (71-80)-(74-80) (Box 28.1, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (1-84)-(10-84) (Box 28.1, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (6-84)-(10-84) (Box 28.1, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (11-84)-(22-84) (Box 28.1, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (23-84)-(35-84) (Box 28.1, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (36-84)-(50-84) (Box 28.1, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (51-84)-(62-84) (Box 28.1, Folder 7)
- SSR Letters: (63-84)-(75-84) (Box 28.2, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (76-84)-(90-84) (Box 28.2, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (91-84)-(100-84) (Box 28.2, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (1-85)-(15-85) (Box 28.2, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (16-85)-(30-85) (Box 28.2, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (31-85)-(35-85) (Box 28.2, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (36-85)-(50-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (51-85)-(65-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (66-85)-(75-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (77-85)-(85-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (77-85)-(85-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (86-85)-(100-85) Missing: (91-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (106-85)-(110-85) (Box 28.3, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (36-84)-(50-84) Missing (37-84) (Box 28.4, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (50-84)-(60-84) (Box 28.4, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (61-84)-(74-84) (Box 28.4, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (103-85) (Box 28.4, Folder 4)
- SSR Letters: (111-85)-(125-85) (Box 28.4, Folder 5)
- SSR Letters: (1-86)-(5-86) (Box 28.4, Folder 6)
- SSR Letters: (31-86)-(35-86) (Box 28.4, Folder 7)
- SSR Letters: (46-86)-(55-86) (Box 28.4, Folder 8)
- SSR Letters: (56-86)-(67-86) (Box 28.5, Folder 1)
- SSR Letters: (68-86)-(80-86) (Box 28.5, Folder 2)
- SSR Letters: (61-87)-(65-87) (Box 28.5, Folder 3)
- SSR Letters: (77-87)-(90-87) (Box 28.5, Folder 4)
- Health and Welfare, National Level (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Health and Welfare Movement (Box 29, Folder 2)
- 1971 Health and Welfare Movement (Box 29, Folder 3)
- RR Act Amendment 1983 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Letters W-1 through W-7, Missing W-3 and W-4 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Letters W-3 through W-8, Missing W-4 and W-7, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Misc. WR Letters 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Misc. WR Letters 1978-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- "Wage and Rules" 1981 Volume III (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Wage-Rule Movement (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Wage and Rules 1981 Volume IV (Box 30.1, Folder 1)
- Wage and Rules 1981 Volume II (Box 30.1, Folder 2)
- Wage and Rules 1981 Volume I (Box 30.1, Folder 3)
- Wage and Rules 1981 Volume V (Box 30.2, Folder 1)
- Wage and Rules 1981 Volume VI (Box 30.2, Folder 2)
- Wages-Rules 1981 (Box 30.2, Folder 3)
- "Wages and Rules" 1978 (Box 30.2, Folder 4)
- Work-Rules Letters (Box 30.2, Folder 5)
- Canadian Wage-Rules 1982-1983 (Box 30.2, Folder 6)
- Local Unions- Ritual (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Election of local officers (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Duplicates and Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 3)
- BRT Locals (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Jurisdiction and Authority (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Merging (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Rescinding Characters (Box 31, Folder 7)
- SUNA Locals- discontinued and merged directory (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Transfers- "S" Locals to "T" Locals and L-M Reports (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Record of Active and Defunct Locals- SUNA (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Officers- "S" Locals and General Committees (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Potential Consolidation- General Instructions (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Election of Officers (Box 31.1, Folder 1)
- Local 283 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Local 293 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Local 281- "Torpedo" (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Local 232 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Local 324 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- "454 News" (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Local 527 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Local 720 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Local 807 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Local 830 "Drawbar" (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Local 1000 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Local 1031 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Local 1221 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Local 1290 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Local 1336 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- #1382 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Local 1532 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Local 1570 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Local 1801 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Local 1827 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Vol. 5- 1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Vol. 4- 1972 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Vol. 3- 1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Vol. 2- 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Vol. 1- 1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Vol.14- 1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Vol. 13- 1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Vol. 12- 1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Vol. 11- 1979 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Vol. 10- 1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Vol. 9- 1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Vol. 8- 1976 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Vol. 7- 1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- #5139 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Vol. 24- 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Vol. 21- 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Vol. 20- 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Vol. 19- 1987 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Vol. 18- 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Vol.17- 1985 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Vol. 16- 1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Vol. 15- 1983 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Vol.14- 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Vol.13- 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Vol.12- 1980 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- UTU News (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Vol. 27- 1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Vol. 25- 1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Vol. 20- 1988 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Vol. 19- 1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Vol. 18- 1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Vol. 17- 1985 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Vol. 15- 1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Vol. 14- 1982 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Vol. 13- 1981 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Vol. 12- 1980 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Vol. 11- 1979 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Vol. 10- 1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Vol. 9- 1977 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Vol. 8- 1976 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Vol. 7- 1975 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Vol. 6- 1974 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Vol. 5- 1973 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Vol. 4- 1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Vol. 3- 1971 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Vol. 1- 1969 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- UTU Scholarship Programs (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Canadian Wage-Rules Referendum 1971 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- "Construction and Interpretation of Agreements" (Box 40, Folder 1)
- "National Master Freight Agreement and Central States Area Local Cartage" (Box 40, Folder 2)
- "National Master Freight Agreement and Central States Area Over the Road" (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Agreements (Box 40, Folder 4)
- 1973 (and earlier) wage rates and related materials (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Nat'l Agreements- UTU, BLE- 1969 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Firemen Dispute 1972 Agreements, manning, training (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Firemen Dispute- 4/69-5/71 Litigation, Carrier Agreements, 1969-1971 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- 1972 National Agreement (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Nat'l Carriers' Conf. Committee- Agreements and Disputes (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Indiana Railroad Co. Agreements (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Burlington Northern Inc. Dispute (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Co. Dispute (Box 40, Folder 13)
- "Crew Consist Agreement" (Box 40.1, Folder 1)
- "General Labor Agreement" (Box 40.1, Folder 2)
- "Agreement Between Galveston Wharves and United Transportation Union" (Box 40.1, Folder 3)
- "Galveston Wharves Schedule Governing Rates, Rules, and Working Conditions for Enginemen" (Box 40.1, Folder 4)
- "Agreement Between Galveston Wharves and its employees represented by United Transportation Union" (Box 40.1, Folder 5)
- "Agreement Between Chicago, Central & Pacific Railroad Company and its employees represented by UTU" (Box 40.1, Folder 6)
- Georgia Northern Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 7)
- Alton and Southern Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 8)
- Southern Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 9)
- Amtrak Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 10)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 11)
- Canadian National Railway Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 12)
- Cedar Valley Railroad Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 13)
- Chessie and CSX Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 14)
- Houston Belt Agreement (Box 40.1, Folder 15)
- Central Pacific Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 16)
- Burlington Northern Inc. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 17)
- Illinois Central Gulf RR Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 18)
- Missouri Pacific RR Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 19)
- Grand Trunk Western RR Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 20)
- Green Bay and Western RR Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 21)
- Delaware and Hudson Railway Co. Agreements (Box 40.1, Folder 22)